<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Advanced Observability with AppDynamics on AppDynamics Workshop</title>
    <link>/en/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Advanced Observability with AppDynamics on AppDynamics Workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/en/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Event Engine</title>
      <link>/en/20_getting_started/1_aws_event_engine.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/20_getting_started/1_aws_event_engine.html</guid>
      <description>Logging into AWS Event Engine To complete this workshop, you are provided with an AWS account via the AWS Event Engine service. A 12-digit hash will be provided to you by event staff - this is your unique access code. eg:
e8476543c00e  Go to https://dashboard.eventengine.run to log into AWS Event Engine.  Enter your unique 12-digit hash code and choose Accept Terms &amp;amp; Login.  Choose AWS Console, then Open AWS Console.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create Cloud9 Workspace</title>
      <link>/en/30_workshop_setup/1_create_cloud9.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/30_workshop_setup/1_create_cloud9.html</guid>
      <description>The Cloud9 workspace should be built by an IAM user with Administrator privileges, not the root account user. Please ensure you are logged in as an IAM user, not the root account user.
This workshop was designed to run in the Oregon (us-west-2) region. Please don&amp;rsquo;t run in any other region. Future versions of this workshop will expand region availability, and this message will be removed.
--Ad blockers, javascript disablers, and tracking blockers should be disabled for the cloud9 domain, or connecting to the workspace might be impacted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review AD Financial</title>
      <link>/en/50_mobilize/1_review_app.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/50_mobilize/1_review_app.html</guid>
      <description>AD Financial Web Site Before we login to the AppDynamics console to observe the pre-modernized version of the application, let&amp;rsquo;s take a quick look at the web interface of the application from an end users perspective.
Use the following steps to find the URL to the web site:
1 . Go to your Cloud9 console and click on the Preview option at the top
2 . Then select Preview Running Application from the drop down</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Workshop Cleanup</title>
      <link>/en/80_wrapup/1_workshop_teardown.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/80_wrapup/1_workshop_teardown.html</guid>
      <description>In order to prevent charges to your AWS account, we recommend cleaning up the infrastructure that was created. If you plan to keep things running so you can examine the workshop a bit more, please remember to do the cleanup when you are done. It is very easy to leave things running in an AWS account, forget about it, and then accrue charges.
🔹 Execute the commands below to cleanup all workshop resources:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title> Flow Maps</title>
      <link>/en/50_mobilize/2_flowmaps.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/50_mobilize/2_flowmaps.html</guid>
      <description>Navigate to the APM Application Once you have logged into the AppDynamics controller, you should see the home page. Let&amp;rsquo;s start by finding the pre-modernized version of the AD Financial APM (App Performance Monitoring) application and open it to investigate the flow map.
In the Applications tile, you should see the application named like &amp;lt;your_lab_user_name&amp;gt;-AD-Fin-PreMod
Click on the application name to drill into the flow map view for the application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>AWS Account</title>
      <link>/en/20_getting_started/2_aws_account.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/20_getting_started/2_aws_account.html</guid>
      <description>You are responsible for the cost of the AWS services used while running this workshop in your AWS account.
Your account must have the ability to create new IAM roles and scope other IAM permissions.
Create an account   If you don&amp;rsquo;t already have an AWS account with Administrator access: create one now
  Once you have an AWS account, ensure you are following the remaining workshop steps as an IAM user with administrator access to the AWS account: Create a new IAM user to use for the workshop</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create IAM Role for Workspace</title>
      <link>/en/30_workshop_setup/2_create_iam_role.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/30_workshop_setup/2_create_iam_role.html</guid>
      <description>1 . Follow this deep link to create an IAM role with Administrator access.
2 . Confirm that AWS service and EC2 are selected, then click Next to view permissions.
3 . Confirm that AdministratorAccess is checked, then click Next: Tags to assign tags.
4 . Take the defaults, and click Next: Review to review.
5 . Enter AppD-Workshop-Admin for the Name, and click Create role.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attach IAM Role to Workspace</title>
      <link>/en/30_workshop_setup/3_attach_iam_role.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/30_workshop_setup/3_attach_iam_role.html</guid>
      <description>1 . Follow this deep link to find your Cloud9 EC2 instance.
2 . Select the instance, then choose Actions / Security / Modify IAM Role
3 . Choose AppD-Workshop-Admin from the IAM Role drop down, and select Save</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Business Transactions</title>
      <link>/en/50_mobilize/3_business_txns.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/50_mobilize/3_business_txns.html</guid>
      <description>The Value of Business Transactions In AppDynamics a business transaction represents the data processing flow for a request, most often a user request. In real-world terms, many different components and dependencies in your application may interact to provide services to fulfill the following types of requests:
 In a financial application, operations such as applying for a loan, buying or selling stocks In an e-commerce application, a user searching for items, adding items to the cart, checking out In a content portal, a user requests content such as sports, business or entertainment news  AppDynamics orients performance monitoring around business transactions so you can focus on the performance of your application components from the end user perspective.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Servers and Containers</title>
      <link>/en/50_mobilize/4_servers_containers.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/50_mobilize/4_servers_containers.html</guid>
      <description>Servers View AppDynamics provides a correlated view of the servers or hosts that your application components are running on. It&amp;rsquo;s important to assess the current resource usage patterns of the infrastructure your application is running on to have an informed and accurate modernization plan.
Let&amp;rsquo;s look at the host metrics of the server that our pre-modernized application is running on.
1 . Click on the Servers option on the left menu.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update Cloud9 Workspace</title>
      <link>/en/30_workshop_setup/4_cloud9_update.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/30_workshop_setup/4_cloud9_update.html</guid>
      <description>Cloud9 normally manages IAM credentials dynamically. This isn’t currently compatible with the EKS IAM authentication, so we will disable it and rely on the IAM role instead.
 Return to your workspace and click the gear icon (in top right corner), or click to open a new tab and choose “Open Preferences” Select AWS Settings Turn OFF AWS managed temporary credentials Close the Preferences tab  Validate the IAM Role Use the GetCallerIdentity CLI command to validate that the Cloud9 IDE is using the correct IAM role.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>End User Monitoring</title>
      <link>/en/50_mobilize/5_browser_rum.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/50_mobilize/5_browser_rum.html</guid>
      <description>Navigate to the BRUM Application Let&amp;rsquo;s start by finding the pre-modernized version of the AD Financial BRUM (Browser Real User Monitoring) application and open it using the steps below.
1 . Click on the Home option on the top menu.
 In the User Experience tile, you should see the application named like &amp;lt;your_lab_user_name&amp;gt;-AD-Fin-PreMod-Web  2 . Click on the application name to open the Overview Dashboard for the application.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start Your Engines ! </title>
      <link>/en/30_workshop_setup/5_start_engines.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/30_workshop_setup/5_start_engines.html</guid>
      <description>You must have enough available VPCs, Elastic IPs, and NAT Gatweways in the region you are working in to successfully create an EKS Cluster with a managed node group of 2 nodes.
Let&amp;rsquo;s do this !  Now that you&amp;rsquo;ve got all the prerequisites out of the way, you can kick off the final setup steps and go grab a cup of Java  while the setup utility does the rest.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Databases</title>
      <link>/en/50_mobilize/6_databases.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/50_mobilize/6_databases.html</guid>
      <description>XXXXXXXX: The Cloud9 workspace should be built by an IAM user with Administrator privileges, not the root account user. Please ensure you are logged in as an IAM user, not the root account user.
--This workshop was designed to run in the Oregon (us-west-2) region. Please don&amp;rsquo;t run in any other region. Future versions of this workshop will expand region availability, and this message will be removed.
--Ad blockers, javascript disablers, and tracking blockers should be disabled for the cloud9 domain, or connecting to the workspace might be impacted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Summary</title>
      <link>/en/50_mobilize/7_summary.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/50_mobilize/7_summary.html</guid>
      <description>XXXXXXXX: The Cloud9 workspace should be built by an IAM user with Administrator privileges, not the root account user. Please ensure you are logged in as an IAM user, not the root account user.
--This workshop was designed to run in the Oregon (us-west-2) region. Please don&amp;rsquo;t run in any other region. Future versions of this workshop will expand region availability, and this message will be removed.
--Ad blockers, javascript disablers, and tracking blockers should be disabled for the cloud9 domain, or connecting to the workspace might be impacted.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>