<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Workshop Setup on AppDynamics Workshop</title>
    <link>/en/30_workshop_setup.html</link>
    <description>Recent content in Workshop Setup on AppDynamics Workshop</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-US</language>
    
	<atom:link href="/en/30_workshop_setup/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Create Cloud9 Workspace</title>
      <link>/en/30_workshop_setup/1_create_cloud9.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/30_workshop_setup/1_create_cloud9.html</guid>
      <description>The Cloud9 workspace should be built by an IAM user with Administrator privileges, not the root account user. Please ensure you are logged in as an IAM user, not the root account user.
This workshop was designed to run in the Oregon (us-west-2) region. Please don&amp;rsquo;t run in any other region. Future versions of this workshop will expand region availability, and this message will be removed.
--Ad blockers, javascript disablers, and tracking blockers should be disabled for the cloud9 domain, or connecting to the workspace might be impacted.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Create IAM Role for Workspace</title>
      <link>/en/30_workshop_setup/2_create_iam_role.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/30_workshop_setup/2_create_iam_role.html</guid>
      <description>1 . Follow this deep link to create an IAM role with Administrator access.
2 . Confirm that AWS service and EC2 are selected, then click Next to view permissions.
3 . Confirm that AdministratorAccess is checked, then click Next: Tags to assign tags.
4 . Take the defaults, and click Next: Review to review.
5 . Enter AppD-Workshop-Admin for the Name, and click Create role.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Attach IAM Role to Workspace</title>
      <link>/en/30_workshop_setup/3_attach_iam_role.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/30_workshop_setup/3_attach_iam_role.html</guid>
      <description>1 . Follow this deep link to find your Cloud9 EC2 instance.
2 . Select the instance, then choose Actions / Security / Modify IAM Role
3 . Choose AppD-Workshop-Admin from the IAM Role drop down, and select Save</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Update Cloud9 Workspace</title>
      <link>/en/30_workshop_setup/4_cloud9_update.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/30_workshop_setup/4_cloud9_update.html</guid>
      <description>Cloud9 normally manages IAM credentials dynamically. This isn’t currently compatible with the EKS IAM authentication, so we will disable it and rely on the IAM role instead.
 Return to your workspace and click the gear icon (in top right corner), or click to open a new tab and choose “Open Preferences” Select AWS Settings Turn OFF AWS managed temporary credentials Close the Preferences tab  Validate the IAM Role Use the GetCallerIdentity CLI command to validate that the Cloud9 IDE is using the correct IAM role.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Start Your Engines ! </title>
      <link>/en/30_workshop_setup/5_start_engines.html</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/en/30_workshop_setup/5_start_engines.html</guid>
      <description>You must have enough available VPCs, Elastic IPs, and NAT Gatweways in the region you are working in to successfully create an EKS Cluster with a managed node group of 2 nodes.
Let&amp;rsquo;s do this !  Now that you&amp;rsquo;ve got all the prerequisites out of the way, you can kick off the final setup steps and go grab a cup of Java  while the setup utility does the rest.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>